philadelphiaweekly.com 2008-12-17

# about us - privacy policy - philadelphia weekly online

|   
---  
[happy hour  
guide](http://www.philadelphiaweekly.com/happyhour)  
[open house  
directory](http://www.philadelphiaweekly.com/openhouse/)  
[about us /  
contact](http://www.philadelphiaweekly.com/contact)  
[  
  
last week's issue](http://www.philadelphiaweekly.com/?inc=archives_issue&issue_id=457&li=y)

* * *

* * *

* * *

**Privacy Policy Statement:**

  * When does www.philadelphiaweekly.com gather user information? 
  * What are my options to control the use of my personal information?
  * Will www.philadelphiaweekly.com share any user information it collects?
  * What is registered user data used for?
  * What is ad placement data used for?
  * Where is user data stored, if at all?

**When does www.philadelphiaweekly.com gather user information?**

When a user arrives at any _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ webpage their IP address is logged by an internet server traffic statistics program. No personal identification data is gathered at this time.

If you choose to register with this website, on the Registered Users Sign-Up page you will be required to enter name, postal address, email address, and date of birth. If you check the “remember me” check box while registering a cookie will be sent to your internet browser.

If you purchase an ad online from _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ you will be required to enter your name, postal address, phone number, email address, credit card type, credit card number, and credit card expiration date to successfully place the ad.

We may collect personally identifiable information from you when you provide content to us for display including but not limited to, when you participate in user surveys, post messages to forum areas, submit personals or other classified listings, or to report a problem with one of our sites. None of this information will be shared with a third party.

Also, users have the option to email an article to a friend or to themselves. The email addresses entered here are not stored or recorded. They are simply used to send the email and then are promptly disposed of. This module is not a secure section of _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ and users enter email addresses at their own risk. _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ is not liable or responsible for data intercepted by a third party during transmission from an non-secure website page.

_**Cookies.**_ A cookie is a message that is sent to your web browser from an internet server and stored on your computer's hard drive. You can set your browser preferences to reject all cookies but then you may be required to repeatedly log in to participate in various services or promotions.

**_IP Address._** IP addresses are logged for the purposes of systems administration and report information. IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. If you visit _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ , our servers log your IP address. Your IP address is not linked to anything personally identifiable. 

* * *

**What are my options to control the use of my personal information?**

Internet browsers can be configured to reject cookies or alert you when cookies are being sent. Keep in mind that if you reject cookies, it is possible that some sections of _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ may not function as intended.  
In addition, website users can edit their registered user information by clicking on their username in the top left corner of the site, under the Issue Date and above the sign-out link.

* * *

**Will www.philadelphiaweekly.com share any user information it collects?**

No. Information entered at _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ will never be shared with, sold to, or viewed by any third party organization. You will not receive any unsolicited (Spam) email as a result of entering information on this website.

* * *

**What is registered user data used for?**

We review our users' preferences, demographics and traffic patterns, so we can identify who our audience is, and what that audience prefers. Tracking user preferences also helps us serve you more relevant advertising. Internet traffic information is analyzed and used to make improvements to _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ , and for marketing purposes.

Email address is used to add recipients to the PW eNewsletter mailing list. Recipients have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving the newsletter by following instructions contained in every eNewsletter email they receive. _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ may also use this email address to communicate with you in regards to your account status, major changes to the website, changes in privacy policy, or participation in surveys requesting feedback about your website experience.

This information is also used when website users register for promotional contests posted on _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_. Date of birth is required to enter a promotion for age verification purposes. Name, email address address, and postal address are used to contact contest winners.

Statistics on the number of registered users on _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ will be used for marketing purposes, however, no specific identification data will ever be used in marketing or made public.

* * *

**What is ad placement data used for?**

User data collected during ad placement is used for scheduling of the purchased ad for publication. Name, postal address, email address, and phone number will be used to contact a client in the event of a problem with their ad. Credit card information is used to bill the client for advertising purchased through www.philadelphiaweekly.com.

* * *

**Where is user data stored, if at all?**

Registered user information is stored in an encrypted format on a secured internet server. In addition all information entered is done so from a secure socket layer web page and is encrypted during transmission. Each time a user logs in there is a selectable option for _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ to remember the user. If selected, a cookie containing the _www.philadelphiaweekly.com_ username is placed on the users computer. This cookie is used to identify a returning registered user. A cookie is a message that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive.

Information gathered during the process of placing an ad is securely transferred to a offline advertising accounting/scheduling application. Email address gathered while ads are purchased are stored in an encrypted format on the secure internet server indefinitely for the purpose of sending confirmation emails with specific regard to an ad that was purchased.

| 

_PW_ Online Extras

Gateau Fabulous  
Let's put the guts back in America -- and a real cake back in America's gob.  
12/8 – _in extremis_

Gateau Fabulous  
Let's put the guts back in America -- and a real cake back in America's gob.  
12/8 – _in extremis_
